[
  {
    "question": "S’il vous plaît (seel voo play)",
    "answers": ["Thank you", "Please (formal)", "You’re welcome (casual)", "Excuse me (to get attention)"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "De rien (duh ree-ahn)",
    "answers": ["Don’t mention it/It’s nothing", "You’re welcome (casual)", "Gladly/Willingly", "Bless you! (informal)"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Avec plaisir (ah-vek play-zeer)",
    "answers": ["Thank you", "Please (formal)", "With pleasure", "Cheers!"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Bon appétit! (bun ah-pay-tee)",
    "answers": ["Enjoy your meal!", "Please (formal)", "You’re welcome (casual)", "Excuse me (to get attention)"],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "À vos souhaits! (ah voh sway)",
    "answers": ["Don’t mention it/It’s nothing", "You’re welcome (casual)", "Gladly/Willingly", "Bless you! (after a sneeze, formal)"],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Merci beaucoup (mehr-see boh-koo)",
    "answers": ["Thank you", "Please (formal)", "Thank you very much", "Cheers!"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Santé! (sahn-tay)",
    "answers": ["Don’t mention it/It’s nothing", "You’re welcome (casual)", "Gladly/Willingly", "Cheers! (to your health)"],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Je suis désolé(e) (zhuh swee day-zoh-lay)",
    "answers": ["It’s not a big deal/No problem", "I am sorry (for a mistake/bad news)", "Bless you! (informal)", "Excuse me (to get attention)"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Ce n’est pas grave (suh nay pah grahv)",
    "answers": ["Pardon me/Sorry (for bumping into someone)", "It’s not a big deal/No problem", "Gladly/Willingly", "Bless you! (informal)"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Il n’y a pas de quoi (eel nyah pah duh kwah)",
    "answers": ["I am sorry (for a mistake/bad news)", "Pardon me/Sorry (for bumping into someone)", "Don’t mention it/It’s nothing", "With pleasure"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  }
]

